houseofnightseries.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy | House of Night Series

We at St. Martin’s Press, LLC (“we” or “St. Martin’s”) respect your concerns about privacy and value the relationship we have with you. This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect on [www.HouseOfNightSeries.com](http://www.houseofnight.com/), how we may use that information, and with whom we may share it.  
Our Privacy Notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the information. In addition, we describe the choices you can make about how we use the information you provide to us. We also tell you how you can reach us to update your contact information, contact us with general questions or comments, inquire about our company and its products and services, or answer any questions you may have about our privacy practices.

  * Getting our Products
  * Surveys and Questionnaires
  * Sweepstakes, Contests, and Promotions
  * Chat Rooms, Forums, and Discussion Groups
  * “Contact Us”
  * Other Site Features
  * Passive Collection of Information
  * How We Use Information We Collect
  * Information We Share
  * Links to Other Websites
  * Children’s Privacy
  * Security
  * Your Choices
  * Updates to this Privacy Notice
  * How to Contact Us Information We Collect

### Getting Our Products

On occasion, we may offer giveaways or other promotional items.In these instances, we will request your contact information (suchas name and mailing address) to fulfill your request, and may requestother information that we think is useful or relevant.

###  Surveys and Questionnaires

We may ask visitors to our website to complete online surveys andopinion polls on a variety of topics, such as their activities,attitudes, and interests, and our products and services. These surveyshelp us understand the needs of our visitors.

### Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions

From time to time we may run sweepstakes, contests or other promotions,some of which you may enter online. If you choose to participate,we may ask you for your contact information. In some cases, we alsomay ask you for other information in connection with the promotion.

### Chat Rooms, Forums, and Discussion Groups

In the future, we may choose to host chat rooms, forums and/or discussiongroups on our website. If you choose to participate in a chat room,forum or discussion group, we may request certain information suchas your email address and date of birth. Please be aware that someor all information you provide (including personally-identifiableinformation) in connection with a chat room, forum or discussion group may become publicly available.

### Contact Us

You may choose to contact us through our website. If you e-mailus comments or questions, we will have your e-mail address, as wellas any other information you choose to provide.

###  Other Site Features and Updates to this Privacy Notice

We may from time to time offer visitors to our website various other features, and we may ask for certain personal information in connection with these features.

### Passive Collection of Information

When you visit our website, your browser automatically sends us certain Internet-related information, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you’re using and your originating domain. We also collect certain information about our website visitors,such as how many users visited our site, the average time spenton the site, the pages viewed, and referring websites.  
By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors. While we generally examine such information only in theaggregate, such information could be linked back to individual IP addresses.

### How We Use Information We Collect

Information collected through our website is used in connection with the purpose for which it was submitted (for example, to contact you to answer a question, or to send you information or a product you’ve requested).  
We may also use the information we collect to send you information or products we think may be of interest to you, to customize ourcontacts with you and to do other internal analyses, such as market research, that will allow us to better meet the needs of our customers.

### Information We Share

We do not sell, rent, trade or otherwise disclose personal information about our website visitors, except as described here. We may share the information you provide with companies that are related to St. Martin’s through common ownership. We also share information provided by our website visitors with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. In addition, we may share information about you with non-affiliated third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you.  
These third parties may contact you about their products and services. We will not share your information with these third parties for their own marketing purposes if you request that we not do so. We may, however, engage in joint marketing activities with selected third parties and may share personal information about our website visitors with them. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, (ii) in response to legal process, (iii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iv) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.  
We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about youin the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our businessor assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonableefforts to try to ensure that the transferee uses personal informationyou have provided through this website in a manner that is consistentwith this Privacy Notice.

### Links to Other Websites

We provide links to other websites for your convenience and information, including websites of other companies related to St. Martin’s Press through common ownership. These sites may operate independently from [www.worldwithoutus.com](http://www.worldwithoutus.com/), and may not be under our control. These sites may have their own privacy notices in place, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked website.  
We may not be responsible for the content of these sites, any products or services that may be offered through these sites, or the privacy practices of these sites.

### Children’s Privacy

This website is intended for an audience of adult readers, and isnot meant for children. We do not knowingly collect informationfrom children under 13.

### Security

We use administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect information in our possession and control against foreseeable hazards. Please note, however, that perfect security does not exist on the Internet.

### Your Choices

We give you the option of requesting that we not share personal information about you with third parties that are unrelated by common ownership with St. Martin’s for marketing use. [Click here](mailto:trademarketing@stmartins.com) to send us an e-mail with your name and e-mail address(es) if you DO NOT want us to share your personal information with unrelated third parties for their own marketing use.

We also give you the option of requesting that we not share your information with companies related to St. Martin’s by commonownership for marketing use. However, PLEASE NOTE that, becauseof the integrated nature of St. Martin’s and some of thesecompanies, if you opt out of sharing with them, you will also automatically be opted out of marketing use by St. Martin’s Press. That means that you will not receive our e-newsletter or information from us about books, promotions and services.  
[Click here](mailto:trademarketing@stmartins.com) to send us an e-mail with your name and e-mail address(es), if you do not want us to share your information with related companies for marketing use (or use the information for marketing purposes ourselves). (Keep in mind, however, that some of our related companies may have independently obtained your information, in which case you may continue to receive communications from those companies, unless you opt out directly with them.)

Please be aware that we are able to effectuate an opt-out only for a specific e-mail address. So, if you have more than one e-mail address or if you have changed your email address, your opt out request may not be effectuated properly. If you believe you have opted out, but continue to receive e-mails from us, please contact us by one of the means listed under “How to Contact Us”, below, and we will endeavor to resolve the issue.

### Updates to this Privacy Notice

We may change or update portions of this Privacy Notice at any timeand without prior notice to you. Please check back from time totime so you are aware of any changes or updates to the Notice. Wewill indicate above the effective date of the Notice.

### How to Contact Us

If you would like to update your contact information, [click here](mailto:trademarketing@stmartins.com).  
If you have any questions about our information practices or ourproducts or services, please contact us by:

  * • clicking [here](mailto:trademarketing@stmartins.com)
  * • writing us at:

St. Martin’s Press  
Marketing Department – 16th Floor  
175 Fifth Avenue  
New York , NY 10010  
Attention: Marketing Assistant
